Can't bind to prop name because it isn't a known\h property of node. You may encounter this error\h\h
Can't bind to prop name because it isn't a known property of node.
when you attempt to bind to a property or\h attribute of an element, but that property\h\h
你可能在試圖繫結某元素的 Property 或 Attribute，而
is unknown to Angular. It may be unknown for a\h variety of reasons. If it's an Angular component,\h\h
這可能出於多種原因。如果它是 Angular 元件
it might be missing the @Input decorator on the\h component definition. But if it's a native HTML\h\h
它可能在元件定義中忘了寫 @Input 裝飾器。但是如果它是原生 HTML 元素
element, it may be a property that just does\h not exist. Or, if you happen to be working with\h\h
它可能只是因為該屬性不存在。或者，如果你在使用自訂元素或 Web Components
custom elements or web components, there may\h be additional configuration required to bind\h\h
它可能需要進行額外的配置，以繫結到自訂屬性
to custom properties. Let's start with a quick\h review of how property binding works in Angular.\h\h
讓我們先快速過一遍 Angular 屬性繫結的工作原理
Then we'll examine several reproductions\h and resolutions for the issue. In an\h\h
然後，我們會檢查一些錯誤重現並解決它們
Angular template we can bind to a property,\h by wrapping it in brackets, then provide an\h\h
在 Angular 範本中，我們可以透過把屬性包裹在方括號中來繫結它
expression on the right side. When the value in\h the expression changes the bound property and\h\h
並且在其右側提供表示式。當表示式的值發生變化時，被繫結的屬性
UI will be updated automatically. In most cases\h you'll run into issues with unknown properties\h\h
及其對應的 UI 都會自動更新 通常，你會在使用自訂元件時會遇到未知屬性的問題
when working with your own custom components.\h In our code we have an ItemComponent with a name\h\h
在我們的程式碼中，我們有一個帶有 name 屬性的 ItemComponent
property. Then, in the AppComponent template we\h reference the App Item Component and attempt to\h\h
然後，在 AppComponent 範本中，我們參考了 ItemComponent
bind to the name property. But currently\h Angular tells us it can't bind to name,\h\h
並試圖繫結到其 name 屬性 但現在，Angular 告訴我們它無法繫結到 name
since it isn't a known property of 'app-item'.\h We can address the issue by going back into our\h\h
因為它不是一個 'app-item' 的已知屬性 我們可以透過回到 ItemComponent，並且
ItemComponent and adding the input decorator to\h the name property. The @Input decorator allows\h\h
為 name 屬性新增 @Input 裝飾器來解決此問題
data to be bound or passed in from the outside of\h the component via the template. In other words,\h\h
這個 @Input 裝飾器允許資料進行繫結或者說透過範本從元件的外部傳入
if a property is not specified as an input it\h can't be used with brackets for data binding in\h\h
換句話說，如果某個屬性沒有被指定為 @Input，它就不能
the template. It's also worth noting that you\h can pass an argument to the @Input decorator\h\h
在範本中使用方括號進行資料繫結 另請注意，你可以給 @Input 裝飾器傳入引數
to change the name of the property. That allows\h you to use a different name in the template\h\h
以改變該屬性的名字
than is used as the property name in the component\h itself. In addition to your custom components\h\h
這可以讓你能在範本中使用與其元件內部屬性名不同的名字
you might also run into this issue with native\h HTML elements. With the default configuration,\h\h
另外，你的自訂元件還可能出現與原生 HTML 元素相關的問題 在預設配置下
you can only bind to properties that the Angular\h compiler knows about. When working with native\h\h
你只能繫結 Angular 編譯器認識的屬性
HTML elements it knows about the properties\h and attributes from the HTML standard spec. For\h\h
當使用原生 HTML 元素時，它認識來自 HTML 規範的 Property 和 Attribute
example, here we have an input element and we're\h binding to the value attribute on that element.\h\h
比如，對於 Input 元素，我們可以繫結到該元素的 value 屬性
At this point there's no error, because\h value is a valid attribute on an input,\h\h
這時不會發生錯誤，因為 value 是 input 的一個有效屬性
but if we attempt to bind to an attribute that\h does not exist, then Angular will throw an error.\h\h
但如果我們試圖繫結到一個不存在的屬性，Angular 就會丟擲錯誤
There's probably not a good reason to bind\h to a property that does not exist on a native\h\h
雖然並沒有什麼好的理由繫結到原生 HTML 元素中不存在的屬性
HTML element. However it is possible to tell\h Angular to ignore this error within an ngModule.\h\h
但是仍然可以告訴 Angular 在某個 ngModule 中忽略這個錯誤
Angular core contains a NO_ERRORS_SCHEMA which we\h can add to the schema's array inside an ngModule\h\h
新增到 ngModule 裝飾器中的 schemas 陣列中
decorator. Notice how the error disappears when\h we update the schema. But keep in mind this is\h\h
注意，當我們修改這個 schema 的時候，錯誤消失了，但是要記住
generally a technique that you should only use\h as a last resort because it will bypass the error\h\h
這項技巧只應該作為不得已的手段使用，因為它會忽略所有此類錯誤
altogether which may lead to uncaught issues and\h unstable code in the future. Now one other area\h\h
而這會在未來給我們帶來未捕獲的問題和不穩定的程式碼
you may encounter this error is when working\h with web components or custom elements. When\h\h
另一個你可能遇到此問題的地方是使用 Web Components 或自訂元素時
working with a custom element it may be perfectly\h acceptable to bind to a property that Angular does\h\h
當使用自訂元素時，繫結到一個 Angular 不認識的屬性是完全可以的
not know about. We can tell Angular to bypass the\h error in a more conservative way by applying the\h\h
我們可以用一種更保守的方式告訴 Angular 忽略本錯誤 那就是在 ngModule 中使用 CUSTOM_ELEMENTS_SCHEMA
CUSTOM_ELEMENTS_SCHEMA in the ngModule. This will\h tell Angular to bypass the known property error on\h\h
這會告訴 Angular 在自訂元素上忽略其已知屬性的錯誤
custom elements like your own Angular\h components or third-party web components.\h\h
就像它們是你自己的 Angular 元件或第三方 Web 元件一樣
That allows you to bind to any property on a\h custom element, but you'll still get errors\h\h
它會允許你在自訂元素上繫結任意屬性，但是當
when attempting to bind to a non-existent\h property on a native HTML element. Let's go\h\h
在原生 HTML 元素上繫結到不存在的屬性時仍然會報錯
ahead and recap. When you encounter 'Can't bind\h to prop name since it isn't a known property of\h\h
我們來回顧一下 當你遇到 'Can't bind to prop name since it isn't a known property of node'
node," you'll first want to verify that the\h prop name is known to Angular. While native\h\h
錯誤時，你首先要驗證一下此屬性名對 Angular 是已知的
HTML elements should only use properties based\h on the actual HTML spec, when working with custom\h\h
原生 HTML 元素只應該使用基於現行 HTML 規範的屬性
elements you can bypass the error by applying\h the CUSTOM_ELEMENTS_SCHEMA in an ngModule,\h\h
當使用自訂元素時，你可以透過在 ngModule 中 使用 CUSTOM_ELEMENTS_SCHEMA 來忽略本錯誤
or as a last resort you can bypass it all together\h with the NO_ERRORS_SCHEMA. For additional details\h\h
作為不得已的手段，你可以使用 NO_ERRORS_SCHEMA 來忽略所有此類錯誤
and examples check out the property binding\h guide in the official Angular documentation.
欲知詳情和範例，請參閱 Angular 官方文件的屬性繫結指南